Guide to the Dorothy Lobrano Guth papers, 1972-1978.
Guth, Dorothy Lobrano papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Dorothy Lobrano Guth papers, 1972-1978.
6878
Dorothy Lobrano. Guth
1.3 cubic feet.
Correspondence, Manuscripts, Printed Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Letters, manuscripts, galley proofs, and other materials relating to the publication of the Letters of E. B. White. Includes numerous letters from White to Guth.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Dorothy Lobrano (Mrs. Raymond C.) Guth is the daughter of long-time (1938-1956) New Yorker fiction editor, Gus Lobrano (Class of 1924) and the goddaughter of E. B. White. In 1976, she collected and edited an edition of the Letters of E. B. White.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Letters, manuscripts, galley proofs, and other materials relating to the publication of the Letters of E. B. White. Includes numerous letters from White to Guth.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Guth, Dorothy Lobrano.; White, E. B.(Elwyn Brooks), 1899-1985.; White, E. B.(Elwyn Brooks), 1899-1985.
Subjects:
American literature, 20th century.; Authors and publishers.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- EBW (E. B. White) re C. Mack (Corona Machemaer) 1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- DLG (Dorothy Lobrano Guth) Editorial and writing 1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- EBW - DLG correspondence 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- EBW to DLG corrections 1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Correspondence re book 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Maine trip 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- EBW letters to DLG re book 1972-1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- EBW to DLG November 7, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Christopher S. Jennisen to DLG October 19, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Material for notes 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- EBW correspondence 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Acknowledgements 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Permissions to quote and library material 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Queries to BH, Cornell, EBW 1972-1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- EBW's parents' 50th anniversary wedding booklet 1930 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- EBW letter to Mr. and Mrs. Girard Chester 1973 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Correspondence and articles 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 16-17)
- EBW correspondence 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- EBW correspondence and corrections 1948-1975 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Letters asking for letters - people to write and letters received 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- EBW and editorial matters 1972-1984 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- EBW materials - unprocessed and pending 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Notes and comments from Corona Machemaer August 1, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- DLG notes n.d. (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Galleys 1976 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)